<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description></description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 18:17:43 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 18:17:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Case Study Ximble Wordpress to Jekyll Migration</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;See the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ximble.com/&quot;&gt;Ximble Site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter the CTO from Nimbleschedule called me to discuss a complete re-brand of their popular Staff Scheduling and
time-clock software. At first, he wanted to revamp their current Wordpress site with all new branding and designs. It
made sense, they’ve always used Wordpress, he had over 400 posts dating all the way back to 2011. It was slow,
bloated, and required constant maintenance to keep it secure. They didn’t particularly like it, but this was just how
 it was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I told Peter about the state of static sites these days. It’s still relatively new, and not as mature as Wordpress
yet. But, I explained to him the &lt;a href=&quot;http://templatestud.io/blog/static-sites-vs-wordpress/&quot;&gt;benefits&lt;/a&gt; such as
speed, security and simpler architecture. He saw the benefits because he understood the technology; and also he was a
fellow technology geek.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a person that had to deal with the headaches with CMS’s like Joomla, Drupal, and Wordpress, I kindly
declined his offer to work on the site in Wordpress. Instead, I proposed we migrate the whole thing off of Wordpress
onto Jekyll. Start fresh, like buying a new car, instead of trying to slap a new coat of paint on an old clunker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter said yes, and we quickly got to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily there was a &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/benbalter/wordpress-to-jekyll-exporter&quot;&gt;Wordpress to Jekyll
exporter&lt;/a&gt;, that downloads the current Wordpress posts into markdown format, ready for your Jekyll site. I’m not
going to say the export was 100% clean and ready to plug into Jekyll, but we managed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/ximble-pagespeed.png&quot; alt=&quot;ximble pagespeed&quot; title=&quot;Ximble&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peter wanted a blazing fast speed, and I was going to give it to him. We used &lt;a href=&quot;https://github .com/Ensighten/spritesmith&quot;&gt;spritesmith&lt;/a&gt; to package icons/images into a single sprite and provides coordinates for
 the stylesheet. We lazy-loaded the images so they only load when it’s needed and took care of the critical fold CSS
 so users will have an optimal viewing experience when they first hit the site. The site was very image heavy so
 these things really helped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../../images/ximble-restaurants.png&quot; alt=&quot;ximble collections&quot; title=&quot;Ximble collections&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site had a section broken out by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ximble.com/restaurants/&quot;&gt;industry&lt;/a&gt; where they displayed
the company’s logos of the brands that use them. This was a perfect instance to use Jekyll’s collections functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://forestry.io/blog//forestryio/images/new-forestry-io-cms.png&quot; alt=&quot;forestry-io&quot; title=&quot;Forestry.io&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another big requirement was to have an interface where non-technical marketers can easily create and edit blog posts
without delving into code. Here’s where a great tool I found called &lt;a href=&quot;https://forestry.io/&quot;&gt;Forest.io&lt;/a&gt; came
 in handy. Also, they provide excellent customer support if you ever run into anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the blog, we were able to maintain the original post images from the Wordpress site. The authors were recreated
into an authors.yml file with their corresponding thumbnail images, name, and info. Since there were so many blog
posts, we had to implement a pagination feature to easily navigate through the older blog posts. I used the gem
jekyll-paginate to accomplish this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the hosting, we went with Netlify. They were able to easily connect with our github repo, so the setup was
extremely easy. Netlify is also able to handle form submissions, so all forms on the site are tied to it. Everything
went pretty smoothly, and we were able to deploy a beautiful marketing site/blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ximble.com/&quot;&gt;Ximble Site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 18:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/casestudy-ximble/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/casestudy-ximble/</guid>
        
        <category>webdev</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>webdev</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marketing Vs Engineering Departments</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Whether you are a web developer in your marketing department or you’re in the engineering department building
something for marketing. We have to stop thinking there is a one size fits all scenario for your web dev workflow.
Marketing usually moves at a faster pace with lots of things constantly changing. It is not the ideal
environment for a web developer that is more structured and process driven. In marketing you have to be prepared for
when speakers to your events drop out and you need to update your site. Or when your event venue has reached capacity
and you need to immediately shut off the registration. You can’t wait, and go through the same processes as
engineering to get the job done. Don’t get me wrong, I believe in version control and QAing in my workflow. But, you
have to approach it with a mindset to embrace the chaos that marketing can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marketing projects are usually smaller in scope; like emails and landing pages. Marketing automation
 software has tools to store your emails or landing pages separate from your main marketing website. This is good
 because your assets are completely self contained and you won’t have to worry about it breaking
 other areas of your site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any good marketer likes to test things like their CTA, copy and images. They need multiple versions of the same email
 or landing page. If they are constantly testing, they don’t have time to wait for the developer to test
 everything the same way they would do in engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marketing has tight deadlines and sometimes timing can make all the difference for conversions. That’s why I believe
in progressive enhancement. Think of websites and landing pages as living documents. We are not in the age of the
printing press where once somethings printed, we are stuck with that print until that piece of paper decomposes.
Things change, what might be true one day can be completely different the next. What we put out now can always be enhanced
and updated in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality of web assets in marketing is that they can be dated. We can build something, only to see it disappear a
week later. Marketing requires fresh content to be pushed out to be relevant and attract eyes. So would it
make sense to spend a significant amount of time and resources to build something out that will be used only once for
 the course of a week or month? That’s why I think the project manager will have to think about your ROI when they
 start a web project. The goal of the page or email is to capture leads, the web developer’s job is to make the content
 accessible so people can consume the information easily on mobile, desktop etc. Would it make sense to spend 8 hours
  to fix a small rendering bug on a form input field for desktop users still on IE 8, when you know that accounts
  for 1% of your traffic? Note that the form input will still function, but it might not look the greatest for those
  1% of users. Or should we use that 8 hours to develop something else that can lead to even more leads instead of
  trying to squeeze the last drop of juice out of dried lemon for those 1% of users.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 18:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/marketing-engineering-workflows/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/marketing-engineering-workflows/</guid>
        
        <category>webdev</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>webdev</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Way To Put Marketo Forms Onto Website</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There has been a lot of debate in the community on what is the best method to insert your Marketo forms into your website/CMS. After a lot of research on the topic, I think the best method is to &lt;em&gt;use an iframe to embed the form&lt;/em&gt;. I know a lot of developers will scoff at this idea because using iframes is a big no-no if you want clean code on your site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason we want to use an iframe is because we want to preserve the pre-fill functionality when your visitor hits the page. Marketo cookies the visitor and if they’ve already filled out one of your forms previously, their information will pre-populate in the form fields. This feature reduces friction for the user and increases the conversion rate. This functionality does not work if you use the form embed code or the Marketo API. The user has to hit a Marketo landing page with the form on it. Inside the iframe window is a Marketo landing page with just the form on it. The rest of the page/layout is still your original design and site. Also, another big plus, is that since we are using a physical Marketo form that you can see in your Marketo instance, you can edit the form freely inside Marketo, and see all of your form fills. You won’t have a blackbox if you use the API, that also limits your calls to 1-10k per day (forgot the actual number).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One issue with the iframe method is that it will load the iframe twice, which would mess up your analytics and tracking. Luckily I’ve found a fix for this and will be detailing how to use it below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;============Solution Overview=============&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of having the iframe on the page when the page first loads, I made the iframe dynamically with javascript that assigns the src URL of the iframe at the same time its created. Then I attach the created iframe to the container of the iframe within the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;===============Step 1====================&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First you need to insert this HTML snippet into where you want the code on your website. Note to change out the URL of your actual URL of the landing page with the Marketo form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div id=&quot;marketoFrame&quot; data-src=&quot;https://mkto.your-landing-page-url-location.html&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;===============Step ​2​====================&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insert this javascript code onto your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt;
var iframeContainer = document.getElementById('marketoFrame');

var iframeSrc = iframeContainer.getAttribute(&quot;data-src&quot;);
var loc = window.location.toString(),
    params = loc.split('?')[1],
    iframe = document.createElement('iframe');

iframe.setAttribute(&quot;src&quot;, iframeSrc + '?' + params);

iframe.style.height = &quot;875px&quot;;
iframe.style.width = &quot;100%&quot;;
iframeContainer.appendChild(iframe);
&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 18:19:18 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/best-way-to-integrate-marketo-forms-into-website/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/best-way-to-integrate-marketo-forms-into-website/</guid>
        
        <category>Marketo</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>marketo</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Static Sites vs Wordpress</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Wordpress is used by 25-35% of all websites online today. They have the biggest market share amongst all other Content Management Systems. People use Wordpress because it is easy to setup, the community is strong with a lot of Wordpress developers and there is a huge plugin library to add any feature you want to your site. However, as you may know, the most popular doesn’t always equate to the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I specialize in web development for marketing, and a trend I see amongst other developers is the rise of the static site generator. Popular static site generators include Jekyll, Hugo, and Middleman. These static site generators are perfect for marketing websites and blogs. I’m currently using Jekyll for this blog. The only downside I see currently is you need to be at least somewhat technical to set up a Jekyll site and edit it. But, the good news is, I’m seeing many tools recently that is making it easier for non-technical people use static sites. Tools such as https://forestry.io/, https://www.contentful.com/ or http://prose.io/ that lets you create content like blog posts with a GUI like Wordpress. Let’s face it, once you have a marketing site up, you don’t really need to change it all that much, and if you want to do A/B testing there are tools like Optimizely that can change your site easily using their interface. I think the only things preventing a faster adoption of static sites for marketing websites and blogs  is education. As developers we need to educate our marketing peers about the greatness that is static site generators. 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The benefits of going to static sites:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Speed and performance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Security (no databse to hack)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Minimal maintenance (no constant updates that can break your site)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Usually cheaper to host&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Simpler and cleaner architecture &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/static-sites-vs-wordpress/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/static-sites-vs-wordpress/</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marketo Form Reset</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A complaint I hear from most clients using Marketo is that they have ugly form stylings for their embedded forms. 
Also developers have a hard time styling the forms because Marketo doesn't use the most friendly code for the display of their forms. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made a Marketo form reset so you have a styling baseline on your embedded forms. 
This will help you style your form to match your own companies styleguides without having Marketo's opinionated stylings override your CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just copy the code below and go to your form in Marketo. &lt;br /&gt;
Then Edit Form &amp;gt; Form Settings &amp;gt; Click &quot;Gear&quot; icon &amp;gt; Edit Custom CSS&lt;br /&gt;
Paste the code into the window and save it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../img/blog/form-css.png&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sr&quot;&gt;/* Marketo Form Reset by Alex Wu - June 2016 */&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoRequiredField&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;label&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoLabel&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;font&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;weight&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:normal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;text&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;url&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;email&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;tel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;number&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;date&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;],&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;textarea&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoField&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;select&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoField&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;100&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;%&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoFormCol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoFieldWrap&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;100&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;%&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoOffset&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;float: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;left&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;height&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;px&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoButtonRow&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;100&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;%&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;text&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;align&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:center&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoLayoutAbove&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoRadioList&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoForm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoLayoutAbove&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;mktoCheckboxList&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:auto&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;float&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:left&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;clear&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:none&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/blog/marketo-form-reset/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/blog/marketo-form-reset/</guid>
        
        <category>Marketo</category>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
